$100 while working, $200 while sleeping.
仕事中は100ドル、寝ている間は200ドル。
I've finally applied for channel monetization, surpassing 1,000 subscribers and 4,000 watch hours.
ついにチャンネル登録者数が1000人を超え、再生時間も4000時間を突破したので、収益化の申請をしました。
Since I already had an AdSense account, I used that existing one.
以前からAdSenseアカウントを持っていたので、既存のアカウントで申請しました。
I believe it's all thanks to you, my subscribers, and I'll share everything I can.
これも登録者の皆さんのおかげだと思っていますので、公開できることはすべて公開していきます。
I said I'd share what I can, right?
公開できること、と言いましたが、
There are things I really can't.
本当に公開できないこともあるんです。
If I reveal those, my channel will be ruined.
それを公開するとチャンネルがダメになります。
But if you follow what I'm teaching now, you'll eventually figure it out on your own.
ですから、それはいずれ私がこれからお話しすることをする中で、皆さん自身で気づかれるはずです。
The moment you understand that, you’ll be making so much money, it'll make even Steve Jobs look like an amateur.
それに気づいた瞬間、あのスティーブ・ジョブズも顔負けするほど、
So, don't worry too much about it, and I'll share everything I can.
莫大な収益を上げられるようになるので、どうかご容赦ください。可能な限り、すべて公開します。
The AdSense ecosystem keeps changing.
AdSenseの生態系は常に変化しています。
The logic of Daum, Google, and Naver also keeps changing.
DaumやGoogle、NAVERのロジックも常に変化していますが、
I'll try to keep up with those changes as quickly as possible and share what I learn.
その変化に合わせて、できるだけ早く私自身が試して、皆さんにお伝えしていきますので、
So keep getting great information through me, your Isayang Jobs.
これからも私のチャンネル「イサヤンジャプス」を通じて、有益な情報を 얻어가시고、
And whenever you feel shaky as a digital nomad, stay strong and keep going.
デジタルノマドとして活動する中で、 때로는 휘청휘청할 때마다 마음 다잡고 가시면 좋겠습니다.
Also, I'm constantly expanding my pipelines.
それと、 сейчас パイプラインをどんどん増やしているところなんです。
I don't know how far I’ll go.
どこまでやるか、自分でもわかりません。
For example, you invest in stocks or real estate, right?
例えば、株や不動産などをされていると思いますが、
In the digital nomad world, we do AdSense, AdPost, Coupang Partners, and so on.
このデジタルノマドの世界では、AdSense、AdPost、Coupang Partnersなどがありますが、
But you can't rely on just those because the income fluctuates a lot.
それだけではいけません。なぜなら、収益が不安定だからです。
AdSense is relatively more stable in terms of income.
その中でも、AdSenseは比較的収益が安定しています。
AdSense is what gives you a steady income,
安定的な収入を生み出してくれるのはAdSenseですが、
but the others aren't stable yet.
それ以外のものは、まだ安定しているとは言えません。
So, you need to keep expanding your pipelines, build a base with the ones that survive,
ですから、色々なパイプラインを構築し、その中で生き残ったものを基盤として、
and then keep adding more pipelines.
さらに別のパイプラインを増やしていく必要があります。
To create a new pipeline, you need to have stable lines already in place.
新しいパイプラインを作るには、すでに安定した収益源が確立されている必要があります。
If you do that, you’ll keep adding new things, and eventually, you'll be able to earn money even if you do almost nothing.
そうすることで、新しいことに挑戦でき、将来的にはほとんど何もしていなくても、
Or, you can just post what you need to. Right now, you write blog posts even when you don't want to.
あるいは、本当に必要なことだけをしていればよくなります。今は、ブログを書きたくないのに無理やり書いていますよね。
Because it's trending, right?
話題になっているから書いているのではありませんか？
You write informational posts after studying, even when you don’t know what they're about. But once things stabilize,
内容もよくわからないのに、情報記事を書けと言われるから、調べて書いていると思いますが、安定すれば、その時からは、
you can write about what you know well, what you want to share, and your income will still be stable.
本当に自分がよく知っていて、人に教えたいこと、書きたいことを書いても、収益を維持できるようになります。
That's great, isn't it? Let's keep going together until then.
とても素晴らしいことですよね。その時まで、皆さんと一緒にやっていければ嬉しいです。 さて今日は、タイトルでお伝えしたように、そして、広告が掲載されるようになったので、広告の配置についてもお話ししたいと思います。
For us AdSense users, especially bloggers,
AdSenseユーザー、特にブロガーの皆さんは、
the click-through rate varies greatly depending on where you place ads.
広告の配置場所によって、クリック率が大きく変わることをご存知だと思います。
In my previous video, I showed you how to use mobile full-screen ads.
以前の動画で、モバイル全画面広告の活用方法についてもご紹介しました。
Like that, for us digital nomads doing AdSense,
それと同じように、AdSenseを利用しているデジタルノマドにとって、
writing articles and creating videos are important, but strategic ad placement is also important.
記事を書いたり、動画を作ったりすることも重要ですが、戦略的な広告配置も重要です。
I'll try to place ads well on my YouTube channel too, according to the content I make.
YouTubeも、私のチャンネルのコンテンツに合わせて、広告配置を工夫していきたいと思っていますので、
Please support me, I'm counting on you.
ぜひご協力をお願いいたします。
I think my channel will last a long time if you do.
そうすれば、チャンネルも長く続けられると思っています。
I'll always be grateful, and let's start today.
いつも感謝の気持ちを忘れずに、今日もお話ししていきます。
Today, what I want to show you is...
今日、皆さんにお見せしたいのは、
I want to talk about top ads.
上部広告についてです。
You place top ads, right?
皆さんも上部広告を入れていますよね。
Whether you’ve been doing YouTube or AdSense for a long time or not,
ええと… YouTube、ええと… AdSenseを長くやっている方も、そうでない方も、
the place with the highest click-through rate and the highest revenue is the top ad.
いずれにしても、最もクリック率が高く、収益性が高いのは上部広告です。
So, we can't not put ads at the top.
ですから、上部にある広告は外せないですよね。
Since we can’t avoid it, we cannot overlook this point.
外せないからこそ、その点を無視することはできません。
How you place the top ads can affect your session duration, bounce rate,
しかし、上部広告をどのように配置するかによって、滞在時間や離脱率、
and even your cost per click (CPC).
さらには広告単価まで調整できる可能性があります。
So, you need to place them smartly.
ですから、賢く配置する必要があります。
You’ve just been placing them and maintaining them because they made money, right?
これまで何となく配置していて、収益が出ていたからそのままにしていた方もいると思いますが、
So you just think, "Whatever."
もう、どうにでもなれ、と。
You don't want to deal with the headache of figuring it out, so you stick with it because it's making money.
色々考えるのが面倒くさいから、とりあえずお金は入ってくるし、このまま続けよう、と思っていると、
That might not be helpful in the long run.
長期的にはあまり良い結果につながらない可能性があります。
Today, I'll tell you about a few types of top ad placements.
今日は、上部広告の配置方法について、いくつかのパターンをご紹介します。
First, there are people who place them like this.
まず、このように配置している方がいます。
The first top ad placement I'll show you is like this:
最初にご紹介するのは、タイトルよりも上に広告を配置するパターンです。
When it's above the title when you enter the page.
この場合、広告を最初に見せることができますが、問題は広告の表示が遅れた場合です。どうなるでしょうか？
In this case, the ad might be seen first, but the problem is, what happens if the ad doesn't load quickly?
空白のまま表示されますよね。すると、ユーザーはすぐにスクロールしてしまうでしょう。
It appears as a blank space. Then people will scroll down right away.
最近は、スマホの処理速度も速くなり、インターネット回線も速くなったので、
These days, phone speeds and internet speeds are faster,
コンマ数秒で表示されないと、すぐに気づいて指でスクロールしてしまいます。
so if it doesn't load within a fraction of a second, people notice and scroll down immediately.
楽器を演奏する方ならわかると思いますが、目よりも手が速いんです。表示されなければ、すぐにスクロールします。
As someone who plays an instrument, you know the hands are faster than the eyes. So if it doesn't load, you scroll.
ですから、いくら最初に見せたいと思っても、表示されなければスクロールされてしまうのです。
So, even if you want to show it immediately, if it doesn't load, they scroll down.
また、アクセスしてすぐに広告が表示されると、何を思い浮かべますか？ いわゆる「낚시성기사」のページを思い浮かべませんか？
Also, if there's an ad as soon as you enter, what comes to mind? Those clickbait pages written by clickbait journalists.
そうしたページを嫌う人は、すぐにページを離脱してしまう可能性があります。
If they hate that, they might leave the page right away.
もう一つのパターンは、タイトルの真下に広告を配置するものです。
Another one is an ad right below the title.
これについては、以前スキン編集で設定する方法をご紹介しました。
I showed you how to place it in the skin editing in my previous video.
そこで一度設定しておけば、このタイトル下の広告も、先ほどのタイトル上の広告も、
Once you place it there, just like the previous one,
スキン編集で広告コードを一度設定しておけば、自動的に表示されるようになります。
if you put the ad code in the skin editor, it will automatically appear.
非常に便利です。
It's very convenient.
また、Kakaoアカウント連携よりも広告表示速度が速いため、以前おすすめしました。
And it loads faster than the Kakao account linked version, which is why I recommended it before.
しかし、この方法でも、タイトル上に広告を配置する場合と同様に、
But, when you do it this way, it's the same here too.
広告の表示が遅れると、空白で表示されてしまい、
If the ad doesn't load right away here either, it will appear blank.
デザイン的に良くないと感じたり、
And people might think it doesn't look good.
何も表示されていないと思って、広告を見る前にスクロールしてしまう可能性があります。
Or they might think there's nothing there and scroll up before even seeing the ad.
ですから、特別な理由がない限り、この上部に広告を配置するのは慎重に検討する必要があります。
So, placing ads above like this should be a conscious decision, except for specific situations.
多くの広告を配置することが有効な場合については、後ほどご説明しますが、
I'll explain later when placing these ads can be beneficial.
ここで 말씀드리는 것은、 궁극적으로 연금형 블로그、いわゆる安定収入につながるブログのことです。
But for now, I'm talking about creating a pension-like blog.
2～3日で使い捨てにする記事ではなく、
Not a post that you use for two or three days and throw away.
書いた記事が継続的に収益をもたらし、
I'm talking about blog posts that will keep generating income,
滞在時間も伸びていくようなブログについてお話ししています。
and you want the session duration to keep going up.
そのようなブログの場合、タイトルよりも上に広告を配置したり、タイトルと本文の間に広告を最初に表示させたりすると、
In that case, putting ads above the title, or the ad appearing before the main content,
ユーザーの離脱率を高めたり、
clearly contributes to a higher bounce rate,
可読性を損なう原因になるため、おすすめしません。
and reduces readability, so I don't recommend it.
では、私がお勧めする配置方法ですが、それがこちらです。
So, what do I recommend? It's this:
こちらをご覧いただければ、お分かりいただけると思います。
As you can see here, you understand, right?
ご理解いただけますでしょうか。
When someone first comes to your page, what they want most should be at the top.
最初にアクセスしたユーザーが最も見たいのは、本来であれば一番上にあるコンテンツです。
It shouldn't start with an ad and ruin the design.
最初から広告が表示されたり、デザインが崩れていたりしてはいけません。
The title comes first. The title appears first, followed by the main content.
まずタイトルが表示され、その次に本文がきます。
The main content appears for about four or five lines. And then the ad appears.
本文が4、5行表示された後で、広告が表示されるようにします。
It's still a link ad, so I used a link ad as an example.
まだリンク広告が利用できるので、ここではリンク広告を例に挙げています。
If you read the text above, you’ll be willing to wait until the ad loads even if it's a little delayed.
このようにすれば、上の文章を読んでいるうちに、広告の表示が多少遅れても、表示されるまで待ってもらえる可能性があります。
If you place the ad in this area, you will definitely see the ad.
この位置に広告を配置すれば、確実に広告を見てもらうことができます。
So, it's a great method.
ですから、非常におすすめの方法です。
And I told you before to put the description at the top.
以前、descriptionは一番上に書くように言いましたよね。
So, the most important information, the answer, should be in the first paragraph.
ですから、最初の段落に最も重要な情報、 핵심이 될 만한 내용이 들어가 있어야、
So that people can read the content in the introduction while waiting for the ad to load, for 1 second or 0.5 seconds.
広告が表示されるまでの1秒、あるいは0.5秒の間、
They can read the content in the introduction while waiting for the ad to load.
冒頭部分を読みながら、広告が表示されるのを待つことができます。
The ad appears here. But it might not be an ad they like.
ここに広告が表示されました。しかし、興味のない広告かもしれません。
Or they might want to see the content below.
あるいは、もっと下の内容を読みたいと思うかもしれません。
What will they do then? They will scroll down.
その場合はどうするでしょうか？ スクロールしますよね。
When they scroll down, the H2 tag appears with a title and the main content continues.
スクロールすると、H2タグが表示され、タイトルと本文が続きます。
But as you can see, while reading this main content, they see another ad.
そして、ご覧のとおり、本文を読んでいる間にも広告が表示されます。
The ad should be placed so it can be seen anywhere on the page.
このように、どこにいても広告が見えるように構成されている必要があります。
It shouldn't be like this, for example:
例えば、このように配置してはいけません。
If the content covers the ad,
広告を隠して本文を読めるようにしてしまうと、
people can easily scroll past the ad without seeing it.
ユーザーはいくらでも広告を無視して読み進めることができてしまいます。
So for example, they see the first paragraph and then see the first ad.
例えば、最初の段落を読みながら、この最初の広告を見ますよね。
But they don't want to see the ad, so they cover it.
でも、広告は見たくないから隠します。
Does covering it mean they won't see the ad? They will still see it.
隠したからといって、広告を見ないわけではありません。それでも広告を見ることになります。
If you design it like this, the ad will continue to be visible. If a targeted or contextual ad appears,
このように構成すれば、広告が常に視覚に入り、その中で 맞춤 광고나 문맥 광고、関連性の高い広告が表示されれば、 (このように構成すれば、広告が常に視覚に入り、その中でカスタム広告やコンテキスト広告、関連性の高い広告が表示されれば、)
they will likely click on it if they like it.
興味を引く広告が出てきたときに、クリックせざるを得なくなるのです。
We tend to place ads carelessly, but especially these kinds of ads are not good.
何気なく配置している広告、特にこのような広告は良くありません。
There's a paragraph, then an ad, and then another ad below it.
文章があって、広告があって、その下にまた広告があるというパターンです。
If you do this, the ad will be right under the first ad.
これだと、最初の広告の 바로 밑에 광고가 붙게 됩니다。
You can scroll past all of it without seeing it.
これをまとめて、一切見ないようにすることも可能です。
So when you place ads, don't assume people will only look at the ads.
ですから、広告を配置する際は、広告だけを見てもらえるという 착각は 버려てください。
They will be looking at the main content, and the ads will naturally be within their peripheral vision.
最も重要な本文を読んでいるときに、広告は自然と視界の隅、周辺視野に入ってくる、
You need to keep that in mind. They'll see it like this. They'll see the second one like this.
という計算をしながら配置する必要があります。二番目の広告も同じように見てもらう、ということです。
For example, as I mentioned before, nobody looks at it like this.
例えば、先ほども言いましたが、このように見る人はいませんよね。
Nobody likes ads so much that they look at them like this.
広告が大好きで、広告を見るためにこんな見方をする人はいません。
If it's placed like this, they will naturally look at it this way.
もしこのように配置されていたら、当然こうやって見ますよね。
Like I said before, just put two ads at the top, somehow.
以前お伝えしたように、上部に広告を2つ、どうにかして入れればいいんです
Place them there, and when there is good content in the middle, don't put too many ads.
配置して、途中に 중요한 내용이 있을 때는 광고를 많이 넣らず、
And place ads at the very end. So they can make a decision then.
最後に配置すれば、最後に 결정을 하거나、
Or they can scroll back up and click the ad. I told you about that before.
もう一度上に戻ってクリックしてくれる可能性もあります。
Do you agree? Placing the ads like this.
いかがでしょうか？このように広告を配置することを、
If you want to set it up as the third method that I suggested,
もし、私がいまご提案した3番目の方法で設定したい場合、
how can we achieve this when we write a post?
記事を作成する際には、どのようにすればこのような設定が可能になるでしょうか？
I'll show you.
実際にお見せします。
This is the new post page of my Isayang Jobs website.
ここは、私のチャンネル「イサヤンジャプス」のホームページ、新規投稿画面です。
First, write the title: "Ads will soon be on the Isayang Jobs YouTube channel."
まずタイトルを入力します。イサヤンジャプスチャンネルに、もうすぐYouTube広告が掲載されます。
Thank you for subscribing.
チャンネル登録ありがとうございます。
Okay, I'm just writing that for fun.
はい、このように書いてみました。
I told you about the description before, right?
以前、descriptionについてお話ししましたよね。
Write the description part.
そのdescription部分を書いてください
If you just do what Google tells you to, it will naturally work out.
つまり、Googleが指示するとおりにすれば、自然とうまくいくようになっているんです。
For example, let's say I wrote a description like this. 160 characters.
例えば、ここにdescriptionを書きます。160字ですね。
"The Isayang Jobs channel will soon have ads thanks to the great love of subscribers."
イサヤンジャプスチャンネルは、チャンネル登録者の皆様の温かいご支援のおかげで、まもなく広告が配信されます。
I’m new to YouTube, so the ad placements might be annoying,
YouTubeは初心者なので、広告の配置にご不満を感じられるかもしれませんが、
but if you keep supporting me as you have been, I will provide you with more tips as an AdSense and digital nomad.
これまでと変わらず応援していただければ、これからもAdSenseとデジタルノマドとして、
I will give you tips on how to have an easygoing life.
平穏に暮らしていくための秘訣をお伝えしていきたいと思います。
I've subtly revealed my true feelings, and now you've written the description.
このように、自分の本音をそれとなく出しながら、とりあえずこのように書きましたよね
We agreed to write the description like this, right?
descriptionはこのように書くことにしましたよね。私と一緒に。
Then you can put an ad.
その次に広告を挿入します。
Leave a space and create the ad placement.
一行空けて、広告を配置する場所を作ります。
Create it like this and then, here is the top ad placement method.
このように作成し、ここに 上部広告の配置方法
An H2 tag will be placed like this.
というH2タグが入ります。
The tag will be inserted, and more content will be below it.
タグが入り、その下にまた文章が入ります。
Content will be written like this.
このように文章が入ります。
So, one space here, two spaces here. This is my style. I like this.
一行、そしてここは二行空けます。これは私のやり方です。私はこれが好きです。
I don't like to put them too close together.
あえてぴったりとはくっつけません。
I like to clearly show the ads.
確実に広告を表示させたいからです。
And then, go to the HTML and place the AdSense ad in this part.
そして、HTMLに移動して、この部分にAdSense広告を挿入します。
Then, when you return, it will be like this. This is the ad part. Some people place ads using the form,
そうすると、このように表示されます。 書式で挿入する方もいますが、
but in my experience, this is just my feeling,
私の経験上、私の感覚では、
it seems like the new editor breaks the AdSense ads a little more when you place them using the form.
新しいエディタで書式を使って挿入すると、AdSense広告が崩れてしまうように感じることがあります。
It may not be true.
そうではないかもしれませんが。
So, it's your choice, but I still place ads directly using the HTML code.
ですから、ご自身の判断になりますが、私はまだHTMLコードで直接挿入しています。
So, put in two lines of description, leave one space, and place the AdSense ad.
このように、descriptionを2行書き、一行空けてAdSense広告を挿入し、
Leave two spaces and then start writing your content.
二行空けてから、本格的に文章を書き始めれば、
Just like we saw on the blog, the first four lines.
先ほどのブログで見たように、最初に4行、
On a typical phone, whether it's an iPhone or Galaxy, the main content will appear for about four lines.
一般的なスマートフォン、iPhoneやGalaxyで4行ほどの本文が表示され、
The title will be above it, and the ad will take up 50% of the rest of the screen.
上にタイトルが表示されます。残りの画面の半分が広告で埋まります。
You only need to place one ad here.
ここに広告は一つだけにする必要があります。
If you put two, what happens is you look at the ad, right?
二つ入れるとどうなるかというと、広告を見ますよね。
You see it and scroll down. And then there's another ad.
見てからスクロールします。スクロールしたらまた広告なんです。
Then you will start to quickly scroll down.
そうすると、どんどんスクロールしてしまいます。
And then it doesn't go the way we intended.
そして、私たちの意図したようにページを読んでもらえなくなるのです。
So, just one ad here.
ですから、ここは広告は一つだけ。
Whether you put a display ad or a link ad, place it like this.
ディスプレイ広告でもリンク広告でも、このように配置すれば良いでしょう。
Then you can use the top ads like this.
これで、上部広告をこのように使用することができます。
The method I didn't recommend before is the one above, this one.
先ほどおすすめしなかったのは、この上の配置方法です。
This method can cause the ad to load slowly.
この配置方法は、広告の表示が遅れる可能性があり、
And even if the ad loads, people didn't come to see the ad.
たとえ広告が表示されても、もともと広告を見ようと思ってアクセスしたわけではないので、
They scroll down, and they can push away the ad and just view the content.
スクロールして、ここから広告は無視して読むことができます。
Even putting an ad above the title might be good in some cases.
さらに、このタイトルの上に広告を掲載することも、良い場合もあります。
If you’re only focusing on trending keywords, it's a bit different.
もし、検索ワードランキングだけを狙うのであれば、少し考え方が変わってきます。
For trending keywords, you need to put a lot of ads.
検索ワードランキングを狙う場合は、とにかく広告をたくさん掲載する必要があります。
Because you'll only be using the post for three or four days.
なぜなら、それは3日か4日程度で使い捨てる記事だからです。
It's a post that's going to bring in 50,000 visitors in 3 days, attracting 10,000 or 15,000 visitors a day, and then you will throw it away.
1日に1万人、あるいは1万5千人がアクセスして、3日間で5万人を一時的に集めて終わる、お祭り騒ぎのような投稿です。
So, session duration is not important.
ですから、滞在時間などは気にする必要はありません。
You need to make sure people see the ads as much as possible.
そのような場合は、とにかく広告を人々の目に多く触れさせる必要があるため、
So, you can put them above, here, there, and even put two ads at a time.
この上にも掲載し、ここにも掲載し、ここにも掲載し、広告を一度に二つ掲載したりします。
Doing it this way is effective.
このようなやり方は効果的です。
The top ad placement that I'm talking about now is for posts that you want to keep ranking on Google,
私が今申し上げているこの上部広告の配置は、Googleで継続的に露出したい、
that you want to use like a pension, and if you write really good, valuable content,
年金のように継続的に収入を得たい場合や、本当に良く書けた、価値のある記事を書いて、
that users will find helpful,
ユーザーがこれを読んで役に立ったと思えるような記事を書くときは、
placing the ads before the main content isn't very helpful, that’s what I’m trying to say.
広告の配置が本文よりも先に来ることは、あまり役に立たないということを申し上げているのです。
I used to put them at the very top.
私も昔は、一番上に무조건 入れていました。
I would always put them at the top and place as many ads as possible, here, there, in the middle, everywhere.
無条件に入れて、広告をとにかくたくさん、ここにも入れて、あそこにも入れて、真ん中にもずっと入れて、至るところに全部入れていました。
As a result, the speed was slow, and there was no improvement. It was all just hard work.
結果は、表示速度も遅くなり、発展がなかったんです。ひたすら大変でした。
I was doing a lot of digital labor.
デジタル作業をものすごくしたんです。
But after changing my ad placements,
しかし、広告の配置を変えてからというものは、
the posts that were generating revenue had a higher click-through rate, higher revenue,
収益を上げてくれる記事のクリック率も上がり、収益も上がり、
and were more stable. And as a content provider,
より安定的に、そして記事を提供する側としても、
I used to feel a sense of shame for writing clickbait and things like that.
以前は、釣り記事を書いて、そのようなことに対して、自分自身でも少し自責の念に駆られ、
I didn't feel good about it.
あまり気分が良くありませんでした。
I always said to my wife,
その頃、私はいつも心の中で妻にも、
I would say “This clickbait is really hard on my mental health.”
ああ、まるでゴシップ記事みたいなのは、本当に精神的にきつい と話したことがありました。
But now, while I expect the revenue to naturally come, I'm writing the content to be most helpful for users.
しかし今は、収益は当然ついてくるものと期待しながら、ユーザーにとって最も 도움이 되는 방식으로、
And I started thinking about the ad placement while I was trying to do that.
記事を書くように努力するようになってから、このような広告配置についても考えるようになったのです。
I thought about how to do it in a way that is helpful to the users and doesn’t violate Google AdSense policies.
ユーザーの立場で、Google AdSenseのポリシーに違反しない範囲で、どうすれば良いかを悩みながら書いたところ、
As a result, it actually became helpful to the users, and as the poster, I didn't feel ashamed.
実際にユーザーの役に立ち、記事を書く発信者である私も自責の念にかられることなく、
Right, and the revenue went up.
そうですよね、そして収益も上がるようになりました。
Of course, I'm not saying this is the correct answer.
もちろん、これが正解だと申し上げているわけではありません。
There may be other ways that work well when it comes to top ads, but
上部広告について実際に色々なことを試してみれば効果があるでしょうが、
If there are people who want to get help from my experience,
私が事前に試した私の経験を通じて、助けを受けたい方がいらっしゃるなら、
then I recommend doing this.
私がこの点を推奨するのです。
So, if you want to create a valuable main blog,
ですから、今後メインブログを少し価値があり、
a blog that will keep increasing in value like a pension,
年金のように着実に上昇するブログにしたいなら、
when you place top ads, let go of your greed and place them from the user's perspective.
上部広告を入れる際、欲を捨ててユーザーの立場で入れることをお勧めします。
Okay, that's it for today.
はい、今日はここまでとします。
There's one more thing I want to mention about top ads.
上部広告関連でもう一つお伝えすることがあります。
I'll talk about that again soon.
それについては、近いうちにまたお話しします。
Until then, try this and see how it goes, I'd be interested in your results.
それまで、今回ご紹介した方法を試してみて、効果がどうなるか期待してみてください。
Ads are most important for us.
広告は私たちにとって最も重要ですよね。
The Isayang Jobs channel is also very important.
イサヤンジャプスチャンネルも最も重要です。
Please take care of us.
ろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
ありがとうございます。
This was Isayang Jobs.
イサヤンジャプスでした。